{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529403380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529403380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529412410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529412409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529429921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529429921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529433487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529433486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529438819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529438819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529442251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529442251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529471165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529471165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529484392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529484391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529488680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529488680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529493320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529493320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529497412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529497412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529501308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529501308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529506982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529506982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529511597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529511596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529516125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529516125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529520706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529520705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529524704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529524703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529529576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529529576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529534481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529534481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529538977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529538977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529543720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529543720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529552231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529552231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529573269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529573269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529577696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529577695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529582157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529582157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529587269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529587269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529590926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529590926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529596698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529596697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529609149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529609148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529674947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529674946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" ce146fda-5b34-44bd-81ba-d2450eab21c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529687768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529687768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529691674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529691674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529693245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529693244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VISU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529696349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529696348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VISU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529697940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529697939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529702112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529702111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529703715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529703714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIJITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529707697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529707696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIJITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529709315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529709314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VITUMBUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529714100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529714099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VITUMBUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529715699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529715699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOLE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529719642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529719641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOLE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529721231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529721231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529725144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529725144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529726727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529726726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529730846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529730846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529732870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529732870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529733027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529733027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529738771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529738770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 4cbe7cdd-acae-43ab-afc3-b2cfe6afea5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529748672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529748672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_R-V-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529752189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529752189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_H-K-V"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529757898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529757898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_S-V-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529761920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529761920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_F-H-V"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529766026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529766026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_F-U-V"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529771549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529771549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_Y-B-V"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529784420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529784419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_E-H-V"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529791435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529791435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_A-V-O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529795456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529795456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_T-K-V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529914449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529914449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_J-V-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529920207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529920207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_V_J-V-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529927256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529927256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 9d71cb7e-49b1-46fb-b167-2d9a60964db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_V_J-V-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529938723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529938723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-2-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529945066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529945066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-2-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529951252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529951251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529957260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529957260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529964130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529964130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-2-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529971874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529971874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529978338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529978338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529985318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529985318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529992127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529992127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548529997999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548529997998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530005828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530005828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530009893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530009893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530016177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530016177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530022531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530022531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530028488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530028488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530035057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530035056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" a0160d3f-6d92-40a8-b921-476d7bf48c9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530049866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530049866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_F-V-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530053305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530053305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-H-D"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530058277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530058277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_K-F-V"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530065016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530065016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_Y-V-F"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530070280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530070280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_G-V-R"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530073727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530073726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_U-V-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530078175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530078175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_R-V-CH"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530083098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530083097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_O-P-V"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530086955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530086955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-H-A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530096103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530096103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_K-V-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530101856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530101855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_220306"," gameId":" 3c6a7e97-92a7-45c8-a902-479bf376a947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_V_K-V-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}